export const createExamData = [];

export const questions = [
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question1",
        answer: "ans1",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question2",
        answer: "ans2",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question3",
        answer: "ans3",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question4",
        answer: "ans4",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question5",
        answer: "ans1",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question6",
        answer: "ans2",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question7",
        answer: "ans3",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question8",
        answer: "ans4",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question9",
        answer: "ans1",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question10",
        answer: "ans2",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question11",
        answer: "ans3",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question12",
        answer: "ans4",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question13",
        answer: "ans1",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question14",
        answer: "ans2",
    },
    {
        options: ["ans1", "ans2", "ans3", "ans4"],
        question: "question15",
        answer: "ans3",
    },
];

// email
// :
// "tecrsts@yopmail.com"
// name
// :
// "aa"
// role
// :
// "teacher"
// token
// :
// "eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJlbWFpbCI6InRlY3JzdHNAeW9wbWFpbC5jb20iLCJfaWQiOiI2NjUwOGExMzNjOTNmODAwNDU1OGM0NGYiLCJpYXQiOjE3MTY5Nzk2NjIsImV4cCI6MTcxNjk4MzI2Mn0.64rZBaY-eDZDdBpRLfd-Fu9lthlVi_WDzPE2qK6xaog"